EDGAR ROSALES

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

6691 870293

✓ rosales.edgare@gmail.com

Mazatlán, Sinaloa, México

in <u>/edgare-rosales</u>

PROFILE

Developer with 3 years of professional experience with web sites, desktop and mobile apps.

Participated in projects with focus to accounting and electronic bill, requiring special attention working with monetary amounts.

Focused on writing functional and clean code from an analytical and critical view.

Interested and open to new areas and technologies in IT.

EXPERIENCE

Microsip

03/2022 - 09/2023

Development and update of modules for electronic bill, payroll, human resources, and accounting. Direct contact with customers to gather requirements and solve specific bugs (Delphi, SQL)

Petromar del Pacífico

02/2021 - 03/2022

Web-app development for electronic billing, generation of reports, payment track and process automation (PHP, Javascript, React)

Menta Digital

PROJECT

Design of web sites and help in marketing campaigns (HTML/CSS, Wordpress)

Huawei Developer Contest México

App development with Huawei Mobile Services integration, top 10 (Java/Kotlin)

TECHNOLOGIES

JavaScript React
PHP Vue

SOL HTML / CSS

Delphi Golang
Git Kotlin

C#

EDUCATION

Universidad Autónoma de Occidente

2016 - 2021

BA. Engineering in Software Development

DELFIN program

CONGRESS

Presentation of an app to learn english